pokefarm.com 2018-12-26

# Privacy Policy - PokéFarm Q

**PokéFarm Q** requires the collection of limited personal information in order to provide the service.

### What we collect

On registration, the user is asked to provide an account name (which may, but generally should not be, their real name), an email address and their date of birth.

In addition to this, the user's IP address is recorded. Additionally, in-game activity does leave a trail that may be used to identify what actions were taken.

Data is stored for as long as the user has an account with the service.

### Why we collect

The **account name** is used to identify the user within the game.

The **email address** may be used to notify the user about important updates to their account.

The **date of birth** helps us to provide age-appropriate content.

The **IP address** and other information related to activity may be used to prevent abuse of the service. This includes but is not limited to cheating or other violations of the site rules.

### Privacy

Other users will see the account name attached to the user's profile and any posts they make on the site.

All other personal information is kept secure. Moderators may have access to certain parts of the information for the purpose of enforcing the site's rules.

No information will be shared with anyone outside of PokéFarm Q, except as required by law.

To comply with the EU's GDPR... we have this policy. Specifically, we don't collect anything that is unnecessary to the function of the service, and don't use it for anything except as outlined here.

To comply with the USA's COPPA, parents of children under 13 may access, amend and remove their child's data on request.

### Accuracy

The user is responsible for ensuring that the information provided to us is accurate.

The email address must be valid and belong to the user. Access to the site will be restricted if a certain time has passed without the user confirming their email address via the activation link sent there.

The date of birth must be correct. We reserve the right to lock the account if we suspect the date of birth may be false.

If you are aware of inaccurate information, please contact us to have it corrected.

### Removing information

You may contact us to request removal of your personal information from the site.

Details such as your email address and date of birth will be removed on request, however access to the service will also be terminated.

Some data, such as activity within the game, cannot be removed. However, if the personal information mentioned above is removed then activity data will become anonymous.

### Contact

If you have any questions regarding what data we collect, what we use it for, or anything else related to this matter, please contact our Support Centre using the link at the bottom of any page.
